# Victoria Morris

(323)788-5792 | vmorris517@gmail.com | Greater St. Louis www.linkedin.com/in/victoriamorris444 | https://github.com/heyimvictoria

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

Highly motivated professional with training in Web Development and JavaScript fundamentals. 1+ year experience learning freelance web development, and 5+ years experience in B2B operations and Customer Success, with demonstrated strong collaboration, training and development skills needed to help establish best practices for a team. Future-oriented, problem solver, ready to pivot into the Software Development industry. Pursuing a career in an organization where utilization of skills in JavaScript, Python, Web/Mobile app development, teamwork, multitasking, leadership, proactiveness will add value to the team and company. Eager to take on coding challenges and learn new programming languages, aiding in the company's mission to create new technologies as the company grows and evolves. the customer experience by delivering great service.

### TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Agile Methodologies
- SCRUM
- HTML5
- CSS3

- Bootstrap Bash Scripts
- UX/UI Design
- Python
- JavaScript

- Google Workspace
- Git and GitHub
- Visual Studio Code
- Code Debugging

## **EXPERIENCE**

Generation USA | Remote | May 2022 — July 2022

Trainee

- Participating in a 21-week Junior Web Developer program learning how software development works, from the fundamentals of JavaScript, computer programming, developer tools, Git version control, and problem solving needed to be successful as a Junior Developer.
- Developed several projects using SCRUM while adhering to project deadlines and deliverables.

Omni Interactions (Contract) | St. Louis, MO | Mar 2022 — June 2022

Client Relations Specialist

- Maintained between 40-50 inbound calls in a fast-paced environment, reducing customer retention by 65%.
- Providing technical support to clients, in regards to, third-party billing and account status.
- Performing testing to ensure product functions, and delivering training for company products

Express Scripts | St. Louis, MO | Aug 2019 — Dec 2021

Patient Care Coordinator II

- Ensures all care coordination, referral dispositions and outcome documentation is completed for all cases
- Maintained inbound and outbound contact via phone with individuals to coordinate care. Increased customer refill percentage 113% with reminder calls.
- Assisted patients in gaining access to community resources including but not limited to; pharmacy related inquires, determined eligibility of applicant, and other program specific functions or medication related activities]

# **Spectrum** | St. Louis, MO | Apr 2018 — Jun 2019

Technical Support Representative

- Handled 50-60+ inbound calls in a fast-paced call center, effectively presenting and discussed Spectrum products and services
- Researched complex issues across multiple databases and work with support resources to own the resolution of all errors and customer issues.
- Achieved profitable growth to meet organizational goals while exemplifying leadership skills to create an excellent customer experience

# **EDUCATION**

### CERTIFIED JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

W3Schools | St. Louis, MO July 2022

# ASSOCIATE IN ARTS — BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION

St. Louis Community College | St. Louis, Mo 2018–2021

#### HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

St. Louis Community College | St. Louis, Mo 2018–2021